<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>QueleAnalytics Blog</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on QueleAnalytics Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact us
 You want more about our analytical phylosophy. Let&amp;rsquo;s meet and evaluate your needs with pleasure without any commitment.
Mail : queleaanalytics@gmail.com
Tel : 04 86 82 84 28</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact us</title>
      <link>/en/nous-contacter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/nous-contacter/</guid>
      <description>Contacter. Contacter
 With plaisure, we come and share with you our enthusiasm and our phylosophy to be &amp;ldquo;data driven&amp;rdquo; mail :queleaanalytics@gmail.com tel : 04 86 82 84 28</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offers</title>
      <link>/en/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/services/</guid>
      <description>We support you for your strategic decisions. Data analysis is a broad area involving multiple technical and functional skills. We intervene throughout your projects to advise you upstream, assist you in the realization and find the answers to your daily problems.
Our offers. Data strategy  A tailored support according to our diagnostics and your needs to give value to your data. We will help you face the new professions of tomorrow: Predictive Marketing, Artificial Intelligence, machine learning and the development of new media solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QueleA is born</title>
      <link>/en/quelea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/quelea/</guid>
      <description>1: QueleA, Context and genesis QueleA ! QueleA was born within my experience in data analytics. What is my experience in data Analytics ?
The almost systematic failure of teams and analytics projects in business.
QueleA&amp;rsquo;s goal is to help in the transition towards digital transformation by building a sustainable &amp;ldquo;Analytics&amp;rdquo; way of thinking.
And why the name QueleA ?
Since I was kid, I am fascinated by this little bird :Quelea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>